Guide to the Matt Kahn Papers SC1094 SC1094
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Matt Kahn papers
circa 1960s-1990s
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Kahn, Matt
SC1094
4.5 Linear Feet
Access to Collection
The materials are partially restricted. Student grade books (box 5) and student/faculty recommendations & endoresements (box 6) are restricted 75 years from date of creation. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Biographical/Historical note
Matt Kahn was born on May 29, 1928, in New York City, the son of Jess and Julia Kahn. He studied at Cranbrook Academy of Art in Bloomfield Hills, Mich., where he met Lyda Weyl, his wife and partner in life and work
When he was 21, Kahn joined Stanford's Department of Art (now the Department of Art and Art History). That was in 1949, and over the following 60 years he created pioneering coursework in design and also taught painting, drawing, sculpture and color theory.
Kahn was appointed assistant professor in 1953 and professor in 1965. He was the director of the U.S. State Department Craft Development Program in Cambodia in 1957-58 and taught frequently at Stanford's overseas studies program in Florence, Italy. In 1993 he received the Dean's Award for Distinguished Teaching and was heralded for his "consistent vitality and enthusiasm" and for being "an opener of doors, a stimulus and guide to the realm of possibilities" who "creates a dazzling environment" for his students.
Kahn's teaching career has focused on design, where he was an active and influential mentor to generations of aspiring designers and talented students. While at Stanford, Professor Kahn also worked as an artistic consultant to Eichler Homes, the developer of modernist homes in California in the 1950s and 1960s. In 1957 and 1958, he served as Director of the U.S. State Department's Craft and Development Program in Cambodia. Professor Kahn has garnered national prominence for his exploration of multiple art forms, from painting to sculpture, textiles, metalwork, furniture design and interiors. Over the years, he has participated in multiple exhibitions at major institutions including the Metropolitan Museum of Art in New York, Portland Art Museum in Oregon, and the Museum of Craft+Design in San Francisco.
Kahn retired from teaching in 2009 but continued to guest lecture for his colleagues until 2011.
He traveled extensively and was influenced by the richness he found in tribal cultures and art from around the world, much of which he collected and displayed in his iconic Eichler home on the Stanford campus. Matt and Lyda Kahn designed their home during the many years they collaborated with Joseph Eichler. It was featured in the New York Times Magazine in 2001.
Kahn's paintings, a blend of precise design, inventive form and a sharp sense of humor, were inspired by nature, humanity and the classical music he loved. His work is included in several art books and has been shown in solo and group exhibitions in Italy and the United States, including shows at the Museum of Modern Art in New York, the San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, the de Young Museum in San Francisco and several exhibitions at the Thomas Welton Stanford Art Gallery commemorating milestones in his teaching career.
Kahn died June 24, 2013. He is survived by his son, Ira (AB Art '72), and daughter, Claire (AB Art '77).
Scope and Contents
Materials include professional files, teaching files (including videos of lectures), and photographs.
Art -- Study and teaching.; Universities and colleges -- Faculty.; Stanford University -- Faculty.; Kahn, Matt; Kahn, Matt
- Professional/Administrative
  - Artwork
    - Graphic Design (Exhibits, Printed Matter, Politics) (Box 20)
    - Model for Furniture Design (Box 23)
  - Audiovisual recordings
    - B.H. Millennium Forum: Matt Kahn, 1997-09-15; 10_05; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 10)
    - Films
      - Unidentified, 1 film reel(s) (16mm)
      - Unidentified, 1 film reel(s) (8mm)
      - Unidentified, 1 film reel(s) (8mm)
      - Unidentified, 1 film reel(s) (8mm)
    - First letter to Italy, 1970-04-05; 10_06; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 10)
    - Letter from Jed, 1970-05-01; 10_07; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 10)
    - John Edmark--Selected Works, 2002-06; 10_01; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 10)
    - Matt Kahn: A Legacy of Excellence, 2010-05-28; 1 computer file(s) (mov)
    - Matt Kahn, 10_02; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 10)
    - Matt Kahn Conference, 1999-06-23; 10_03; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 10)
    - Matt Kahn--Interview at Home, 2003-04-01; 10_04; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 10_08 (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 10_09 (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 10_10 (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 10_11 (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 10_12 (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 10_13 (Box 10)
    - Unidentified, Undated; 10_14 (Box 10)
  - Awards
    - Dean's Award for Distinguished Teaching (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Professional Files
    - Letters from students and alumni (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Curriculum Vitae (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Masi (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit at Stanford, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Publicity (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Publicity-University of Wisconsin (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Publicity-Others (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Tapestry statement; Graphic paintings statement (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Vietnam moratorium (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Extra activities-personal (lectures, juries, etc.) (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Emanu-El exhibit (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CRIA (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Painting (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence-Jiri Bauer (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Kahn, Ira (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Graphics (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - President's Report (Faculty Annual Report) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Design/Body Soul (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - Manuscript and slides
        - Body + Soul, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
        - Publication Info/ Design (Box 25, Folder 2)
        - Overview, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 3)
        - Slides (Box 25, Folder 4)
        - Lectures (Box 25, Folder 5)
        - Lecture Notes (Box 25, Folder 6)
        - Prologue (Box 25, Folder 7)
        - Context (Box 25, Folder 8)
        - Context (Box 25, Folder 9)
        - Context (Box 25, Folder 10)
        - Context; Synopsis (Box 25, Folder 11)
        - Utility, 1999-02 (Box 25, Folder 12)
        - Utility, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 13)
        - Utility, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
        - Propaganda, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 15)
        - Propaganda, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 16)
        - Pleasure, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 17)
        - Pleasure (Box 25, Folder 18)
        - Pleasure (Box 25, Folder 19)
        - Propaganda, 35827 (Box 29, Folder 1)
        - Pleasure, 1992-2005 (Box 29, Folder 2)
        - Vanity, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 3)
        - Vanity, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
        - Vanity (slides) (Box 29, Folder 5)
        - Context (Box 29, Folder 6)
        - Ceremony (Box 29, Folder 7)
        - Ceremony (Box 29, Folder 8)
        - Ceremony (slides) (Box 29, Folder 9)
        - Computer Media (floppy disks) (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Business Card (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Photographs
    - Artwork [transparencies] (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Artwork/Design (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Book Forum--IDEO (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Exhibit, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Fontana art contest, circa 1962 (Box 4)
    - Kahn, Matt (Box 19, Folder 1, Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Recommendations/Endorsements
    Access to Collection
    Recommendations and Endorsements of students and fellow faculty members. Restricted 75 years from date of creation.
    - Julia Rowe (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Corinne Okada (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - James Garland (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bo H. Strandgaard (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Michael Gaillard (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Casey Corum (IDM) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Design Appointment (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Peter MacDonald (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Kelley Appointment (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Interdepartmental Majors Project (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Leslee M. Lewis - Aesthetics in Prod. Des. (Interdepartmental) (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - David Hardesty (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Kevin Owens - Individually Designed Major (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Catherine Morris (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - John Spears (Guggenheim) (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Suzanne Austin (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Peter Guckenheimer (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - ART/CS Joint Appt. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Stanford
    - New Guinea Garden Carvers (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Overseas
      - Italy XIII (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Florence Xmas Card (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Mademoiselle Bonney-Paris Trip (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Italy V (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Overseas campuses (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Artist in residence Summer Firenze, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Italy Group XII (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Italy XII (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Dan Rosenfeld (Italy Project), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Italy Group XX (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Italy XX Spring, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Italy Summer, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Stanford in Italy, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Italy-Autumn, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Scholarship Committees and Other Reports
    - Design at Nine Schools, circa 1959 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Campus Environment Committee (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Faculty Sub-Committee on Overseas Campuses (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Humanities and Sciences Steering Committee (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Committee on Financial Awards (External), 1964 Oct 7 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Committee on Financial Awards (External), 1965 Mar 11 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Committee on Financial Awards (External), 1965 Oct 12 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Urban Studies Committee (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Metropolitan Studies (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - "Fellowships for Juniors" Project (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Freshman Drama (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Expo '67, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - "Design in Nine Schools", circa 1959 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Subject Files
    - Announcements (Kahn Designed/ Other etc.) (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bios CVs (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Cain Project (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Cambodia (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Chair Design (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Conference, 1978 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Cranbrock (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Early Work (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - EICHLER HOMES stationary (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Eslan, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - EXHIBITS (High School Cranbrook, Pfister etc.) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Exhibits - Stanford (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - 50 years at Stanford (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - 60 years at Stanford (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Expo, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Furniture (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Galleries (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Galleria Giorgi (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Graduate Joint Program (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Historical Society - Other History Transcript (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Holiday (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Halloween (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Ideo (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Interlocking can (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - ITALY (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Jewelry, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Kahn Home (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Kahn, Claire (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Kahn, Ira (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Kahn, Jess Julia (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Lectures - slides (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Kahn, Lyda (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - 101 Lombard, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Misc. (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - MISCELLANEOUS (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Morrison Imports (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Museum + Craft + Design 2009 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Others (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Palo Alto Medical Radiology (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Personal (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Pfister partnership (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Press, early (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Press (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Renaissance Symposium in Tuscans, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Publications (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Syllabi (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - TAPESTRY (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - TEXTILES (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Weather Measure Corp. (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - WET (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Teaching
  - Course Material, Data, Photos, etc.
    - Stanford Renaissance Symposium in Tuscany, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Textile Printing and Weaving Data (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Mille Fiore Process (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Design Bibliography (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Jewelry - Technical Info (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - KRON TV Carl Sonkin (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - ASSU - Evaluations and Forms (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - ASSU (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Studio Upgrade (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Studio-Art Report (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - LA Field Trip Spring, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Project Guidelines, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Calendar, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Los Angeles trip, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - AUT 97-Mark Shieh, 1997 Sep (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Sara Little (Turnbull) (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Centennial Campaign - Gold Leaf Mosaic Tile, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Sara Little (Turnbull) (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Meleanna Pricher (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Dean's Innovation Fund/Fine Metal Processes (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Renaissance Symposium in Tuscany, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Clippings - Stanford in New York City (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Department Affairs
    - Epicenter (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Department Review, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Faculty Studio Planning (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Farmer Memorial Resolution (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Faulkner Memorial (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Daily "Design" article Eitner correspondence (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Mendelowitz (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Master's Project Presentation announcement, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Grade Books, 1963-1988 (Box 5)
    Restricted 75 years from date of creation.
  - Graduate Programs
    - Design program propaganda/publicity (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Doria Fan (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lectures
    - Audiovisual recordings
      - Art 60, Undated; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 60, Dec 3; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 160, 1992-01-28; 17_07; 1 audiocassette(s); 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 17)
      - Art 160, 1999 Jan 7; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 160, 1999 Jan 14; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 160, 1999 Jan 21; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 160, 1999 Jan 28; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 160, 1999 Feb 4; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 160, 1999 Feb 11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 3)
      - Art 160: Vanity, Winter 1966; 17_06; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
      - Art 160: Lecture #1, 17_05; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
      - Art 160: Utility, 17_04; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
      - Art 160: Pleasure, 17_03; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
      - Art 160: Ceremony, 17_02; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
      - Cyclops: The Camera Is Not a Butterfly Net, 1996-04-10; 17_01; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 17)
      - Design/Soul and Body
        Scope and Contents
        Title: Design: Soul and Body Course Art 160—Design II: The Bridge Recorded: Winter 2005, Annenberg Auditorium, Stanford University
        Order & Runtimes: 1 Context 1:24 2 Utility 1:45 3 Propaganda 1:37 4 Pleasure 1:35 5 Vanity 1:32 6 Ceremony 1:43
        - Context, 17_08; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 17)
        - Utility, 17_09; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 17)
        - Propaganda, 17_10; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 17)
        - Pleasure
        - Vanity, 17_11; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 17)
        - Ceremony, 17_12; 1 videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 17)
      - Art 60 - 2nd half
    - Slides
      - Design/Soul and Body
- Personal
  - Biographical
    - Modern Masters notebook, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - News clippings, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - PS 89 class book, 1942 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Personal (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Photographs
    - Cranbook football game (negatives) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Family (35mm negatives) (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Family (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Halloween (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Kahn, Claire (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Kahn, Ira (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Kahn, Lyda, 65th birthday [negatives] (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Kahn Home (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Kahn Home (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (35mm negatives) (Box 9, Box 16, Folder 9-11)
    - Playhouse [transparencies] (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Public School 82, Queens, NY, 1942 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Slides
      - 268/78 Kites, Arch, Musicians at Beach (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - 268/88 Portraits, Kites (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - 3 Left (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - 3 Right (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - 3 Misc (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - 4 Misc (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Abruzzi (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Acoma, 31291 (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Africa (Box 5, Folder 9)
      - Air Products Models, 31291 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Alaska, 1968-1988 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Alaska - Juneau Totem Det. / Sitka (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Albi (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Aloma Pot (spiral) / Texaco graphics / Gaudi Hardware/ Cadillac hood ornaments, 36465 (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Aloma Pots / Warehouse X'mas Cover/ Eggs (Robin Stamps), 34001 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Alumni '81 / Italy, Sep-81 / Jul-87 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Alumni Group '86, 31594 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - American Architecture, 62/ '63/ '67/ '72 (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Amemb New Delhi (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Amersfoort / Lyda Anneke (family/ friends), July-Aug 1988 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Amsterdam Boat Trip, 37834 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Amsterdam Dinner, 37834 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Amsterdam Misc, 37834 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Amsterdam/ Holland/ Alkmaar, Aug-1963 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Amsterdam Parade, 37834 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Anneke, July-Aug 1988 (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Antique Cars, Jan-1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Apple Think Different Campaign '99, 36281 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Apr' 62 Easter Family + Egg Hunt, Apr-1962 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Aquarium, 31168 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Arches; Southwest, 31291 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Arches (2), 31291 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Armenia/ Agrigento/ Viterbo, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Arezzo/ Volterra/ Assisi/ San Gimignano, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Arezzo (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Arles (France) (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Art/ Buildings/ Lion Statue/ Clock Tower (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Art/ Drawings, May-1962 (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Artwork - H.S + early (A) (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Art #2 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - Artifacts '91, 33270 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Artifacts/ Halibut Hook/ Ball, 1993/ 1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Artimino, 29830 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Assisi, 81/ '83/ '86 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Athens (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Athens/ Sounion/ Corinth/ Delphi (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Australia (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Auto Show/ Century Plant, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Auto Show, 37067 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Autumn '59/ Ira-Claire, Sep-1959 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Avignon (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Balloon Shelter, Apr/May-1977 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - Balloons, 37135 (Box 5, Folder 53)
      - Balloons, 37135 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Balloons, 28246 (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Barcelona/ Costa Brava, 31594 (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Barcelona/ Concert Hall, 31594 (Box 5, Folder 57)
      - Barcelona/ Gaudi, 31594 (Box 5, Folder 58)
      - Bari/ Lecce (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Bart Magnolia, 34881 (Box 5, Folder 60)
      - Basket, 35827 (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Batman, Donald Duck/ DUCK product/ Cactus flowers/ Arthalts, 34872 (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Bea 80th, 26938 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Bea 90th, Oct-98 (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - Beach Family ('85), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - Beach Personal, 69/ '70/ '73 (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - Beach/ Kites (Personal) '86, 69/ 70/ 77/ 85/ 86 (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Beckey/ Phoenician bead/ Amaryllis vase, 39814 (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Beer Trucks/ Imp Lamp/ Jeweled Mask/ Vans, 1997/ 1998 (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Bekkerman Rings/ Claire Egg/ Boxing Toy, 2002/ 2003 (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Bendon "Bong Tree", Jun-1969 (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Bergamo/ Padua (Box 5, Folder 72)
      - Bergen/ Norway, 29068 (Box 5, Folder 73)
      - Bern/ Lucerne, 62/ 63/ 66 (Box 5, Folder 74)
      - Bern/ Swiss Misc. (Box 5, Folder 75)
      - Beverly Hills, 36892 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      - Bev. Hills/ Star Banners, 36892 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      - Biennale/ Perpignan/ Autopista, 28004 (Box 5, Folder 78)
      - Blimp/ Vallco, 29037 (Box 5, Folder 79)
      - Big Game/ Halloween ('93), 34274 (Box 5, Folder 80)
      - Burney Falls/ Family in atrium (Aug 1960) (Box 5, Folder 81)
      - Blimps/ Easter Eggs (1/93), 33994 (Box 5, Folder 82)
      - Bomarzo/ tarq/ Gamberia, 30590 (Box 5, Folder 83)
      - Bottle opener/ Eye cup/ Gelatin mold/ Toothbrushes/ Cigarettes/ Shaver, 37834 (Box 5, Folder 84)
      - Bottle plant (Lyda) / Troia (Box 5, Folder 85)
      - Brion/ S.Vito, 31959 (Box 5, Folder 86)
      - Brittany, 32325 (Box 5, Folder 87)
      - Bronzi Di' Riaci/ Pots (Box 5, Folder 88)
      - Bronzi Taormina (Box 5, Folder 89)
      - Bruges / Ghent, Aug-1963 (Box 5, Folder 90)
      - Bruner, 29037 (Box 5, Folder 91)
      - Bruges, Aug-1963 (Box 5, Folder 92)
      - Bruxelles Fair (1958) (Box 5, Folder 93)
      - Building Models (Box 5, Folder 94)
      - Bumper Stickers, 36039 (Box 5, Folder 95)
      - Burano (Box 5, Folder 96)
      - Cable (PA Airport)/ Imp Lamp/ VW (blue), 36039 (Box 5, Folder 97)
      - Cable Car, 30834 (Box 5, Folder 98)
      - Cactus Flower/ Agave, 35704 (Box 5, Folder 99)
      - Cacti (834), 32264 (Box 5, Folder 100)
      - Calder/ Miro/ Kites ('98), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 101)
      - Canova, 1991, 33482 (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - Capri/ Napoli/ Paestum, 29160 (Box 5, Folder 103)
      - Carca Sonne (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Carson Mansion (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Cars (MG, Hearse, Cord)/ Masks, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Cats (Bianca/ Ciacomo), 27181 (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - Cactus/ Lemon, 37773 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Candle Sticks/ Table + snakes/ Spratling, 37834 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Canyon/ Sequoia, 38108 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Canyon Lands, 31291 (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Car (hood ornaments/ wheels/ headlights/ Jaguar rings), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Car show, 34090 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Carara/ Masi (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Carpet samples/ Gamble house/ Park Newport, 26024 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Carcassonne (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Carmel Family/ Lyda, Jan-1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Cities, 79/ 82/ 87/ 2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Citywalk/ L.A trip, 34759 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Chartres 1988, 32325 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Chartres/ St. Chapelle/ Notre Dame/ Paris Misc., Jan-1959 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Chiapas/ Oaxaca, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Chiapas/ Tasco, Jul-1965 (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Chicago, 28856 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Chicago (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Chicago United (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Chichen Itza, 26299 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Child (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Claire, Apr-1968 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Claire's 4th birthday, Oct-1959 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Claire 13th birthday, Oct-1968 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Claire 16th birthday, 26238 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Claire's birthday, Oct-1961 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Claire's birthday (10) / Halloween/ House Interior, Nov/Oct- 1965 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Claire's birthday/ Halloween, Dec-1960 (Box 6, Folder 28)